The most wanted men in the west!
From Noon Till Three is a comedy, western film directed by Frank D. Gilroy.
Bank robber Graham Dorsey spends a few hours with beautiful widow Amanda
Starbuck, in which time his gang takes part in a disastrous holdup.
Learning of his comrades' demise, Dorsey goes on the lam.
Believing her short-term lover was killed by the law, Amanda decides to make the most of having
had a liaison with the supposedly deceased desperado by writing a book about him.
Much to his confusion, the still-living Dorsey
watches as his name becomes legendary.
Graham Dorsey, played by Charles Bronson.
Amanda Starbuck, played by Jill Ireland.
Buck Bowers, played by Douglas Fowley.
Ape, played by Stan Haze.
Boy, played by Damon Douglas.
The Mexican, played by Hector Morales.
From Noon till Three is a 1976 American Western film released by United Artists.
It stars Charles Bronson and his wife, Jill Ireland.
It was written and directed by Frank D.
Gilroy, based on his novel.
The film explores themes of bank robber, horse, outlaw, gang.
The tone is lighthearted.